

CONTACT

Address

236, Sai Shraddh Palace, Indore

Phone

+91 9977696202

Email

indrapal.singh1137@gmail.com

SKILLS

HTML 5

CSS₃

Tailwind css

Bootstrap

Js

jQuery

Photoshop

Figma

Adobe Xd

React UI

INDRAPAL SINGH JATAV

Sr. UI Engineer

ABOUT ME

I have 4 years of experience in UI/UX Designer. I am always looking for self-improvement with new possibilities. In rapid and structured progression in the management of my work perseverance and leadership is the primary reason. My design style is clean, professional, and quick.

Every unique creation starts from imagination, followed by dedication. I worked in a challenging environment with honesty and commitment with a determination to apply my knowledge, skills and experience, and professional aptitudes for the organization's success.

EXPERIENCE

Hiecor Software Technologies Pvt Ltd Sr. UI Engineer	2022 - Present
Creative Thoughts Informatics Services Pvt Ltd Web Designer	2021-2022
Brainware Infosoft Web designer	2020-2021
JIT Inspire Web designer	2019-2020
Shiva Concept Solution Business Development Manager & Trainer	2015-2019
NIIT Indore Business Development Manager & Trainer	2010-2013

EDUCATION

Lord Krishna College of Technology Master of Business Administration (HR/IT)	2020-2023
Govt. Arts and Commerce College Indore Bacholer in arts	2018-2020
NIIT Delhi Professional Diploma in Software Engineering (GNIIT)	2008-2011